export const quiz = {
  "quizTitle": "React Quiz Component Demo",
  "quizSynopsis": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is ReactJS??",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "Server-side Framework",
        "User-interface framework",
        "Both",
        "None"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everything in React is a?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "Module",
        "Component",
        "Package",
        "Class"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Babel?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        " A transpiler.",
        "An interpreter",
        "A Compiler",
        "Both Compiler and Transpilar"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many elements does a react component return",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "2 Elements",
        "1 Element",
        "Multiple Elements"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "How can you access the state of a component from inside of a member function?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "this.getState()",
        "this.prototype.stateValue",
        "this.state",
        "this.values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "JavaScript can be used in ____ development",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "Back-End",
        "Front-End",
        "ReactJS",
        "All of the Above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "Props are __________ into other components",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "Injected",
        "Methods",
        "Both A and B",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "At the highest level, React components have lifecycle events that fall into",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "Initialization",
        "Destruction",
        "State/Property Updates",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method in a React Component should you override to stop the component from updating?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "willComponentUpdate",
        "shouldComponentUpdate",
        "componentDidUpdate",
        "componentDidMount"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's used to pass data to a component from outside?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answers": [
        "setState",
        "render with arguments",
        "PropTypes",
        "props"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "point": "20"
    },

    // {
    //   "question": "What are the advantages of React JS?",
    //   "questionType": "text",
    //   "answerSelectionType": "multiple",
    //   "answers": [
    //     "React can be used on client and as well as server side too",
    //     "Using React increases readability and makes maintainability easier. Component, Data patterns improves readability and thus makes it easier for manitaining larger apps",
    //     "React components have lifecycle events that fall into State/Property Updates",
    //     "React can be used with any other framework (Backbone.js, Angular.js) as it is only a view layer"
    //   ],
    //   "correctAnswer": [1, 2, 4],
    //   "messageForCorrectAnswer": "Correct answer. Good job.",
    //   "messageForIncorrectAnswer": "Incorrect answer. Please try again.",
    //   "explanation": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.",
    //   "point": "20"
    // }
    // ,
  ]
} 